

ABOUT

I am a full stack software engineer with a background in business and finance advisory.

I'm a team player and love sharing my experiences and working close with my colleagues and clients. I believe working well with others shows that you are committed to achieving both personal and organisational goals.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript

Node.js

Express

React

HTMI

CSS

SQL

Ruby

Sinatra

Git & Github

Heroku

CONTACT

Sydney, NSW



+61 452 554 307

https://github.com/NicolasJuncal

https://nicolasjuncal.herokuapp.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicolasjuncal/

NICOLAS JUNCAL

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

CHATSUPP

Bidirectional app that allows communication of multiple users simultaneously, developed with React and Socket.IO
Tech stack: JavaScript, React CSS, Socket.IO, Express, Node.JS

WINELOVERSCLUB

CRUD application developed in Ruby. The app is completely done from the Backend and rendered to the client side.

Tech stack: Ruby, PostgreSQL, CSS

TIC-TAC-TOE

First project in javascript. Simple tic-tac-toe game Tech stack: Javascript, Html, CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

WORKSHOP COORDINATOR

Berendsen Fluid Power | May 2019 - Aug 2021

Coordination of a workshop team of 8. Focus on workshop process and efficiency improvement. Collaboration with two IT specialists to implement a new ERP from Fujitsu (RunMyProcess)

BUSINESS MANAGER

Bold Int | Sep 2018 - Jan 2019

Sales of IT services (outsourcing, software factory, IoT). Working in a cross functional teams to strategically tailor a solution for IT stakeholders' demands.

BUSINESS CONSULTANT

HSBC BANK | Oct 2011 - Jun 2016

Wealth advisor assisting with retirement plans, investment funds, tax strategies. Mapping customer needs and plan the best strategy to their profile.

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | 2021 - 2021

MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

KAPLAN | 2018 - 2019

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION WITH IT

FIAP | 2010 - 2015